<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GitLegit</string>

    <string name="john_introduction_info_1">Once upon a time…. John Doe was sick of all the gambling,
        sleeping day’s and walking nights in Last Vegas. </string>
    <string name="john_introduction_info_2">Tired of everything… he just wants to be like everyone else.
        A good job, full LinkedIn Profile, Very Active on Facebook. But the most important thing is finding a job!</string>
    <string name="john_introduction_1">Hello, my name is John I’m 32 years old.
        I’m at this point.Looking for a job. My Friends told me that getLinked is a good way to start searching for work.</string>
    <string name="john_introduction_2">Unfortunately, I don’t have any personal computer.
        Let’s go to the Internet Cafe. I need to go to the Internet Café in the neighborhood.</string>
    <string name="cleaner_job_title">CLEANERS WANTED!!</string>
    <string name="cleaner_job_description">We are a large company looking for cleaners to clean stuff!\n
    The pay is very high, you will be nicely compensated, interested? then please apply!</string>
    <string name="volunteer_job_title">Looking for volunteers, (Minimum wage)</string>
    <string name="volunteer_job_description">We are a small non-profit organization and we are looking for volunteerd
    to help us build several houses for the poor. We are in desperate need of help so you will be receiving minimum wage pay
    If you are interested, please apply below!</string>

    <string name="john_scenario2_1">Once upon a time John Doe noticed he is short on groceries for this week. Help John Doe to find a grocery and take advantage on the discount the supermarket is offering.
</string>
    <string name="john_scenario2_2">Good day Sir, welcome we have a great deal for today. All you need to do is to fill in this form and you will receive a card where you will get daily discount from our store. Great right?..
</string>
    <string name="john_scenario2_3">First you need to fill a form on our iPad and we will print the card for you. It will only take 2 minutes of your time.”</string>
    //sss
    <string name="john_scenario2_4">Thank you for filling in the form. You will receive the deal right away by showing your card to the cashier. She will scan your card and after that you will receive the discount. </string>
    <string name="john_scenario2_4_no"> Thank you for your time sir. </string>
    <string name="john_scenario2_5"> Well finally I got my groceries, but I’m quite hungry now and don’t want to cook something right away. Maybe some fast food will keep me up.. </string>

    <string name="john_scenario3_2"> Too many choices, where should I go? I’m quite short on cash as well, lets take a look at places that give discounts for now </string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_2_5"> </string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_2_question">Where would you like to eat?</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_2_answer_mac"> McDonald’s</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_2_answer_2"> Burger King</string>

    <string name="john_scenario3_3"> hmm looks good, I’m so hungry right now! </string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_4"> Hi Sir! Did you take a look at our great deals for today? You can get 50% discount on anything you order by making a selfie with your order on Instagram, Facebook or Twitter”. Do you want to take this deal?</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_4_5"> You made your decision..continue</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_4_question"> Do you want to take this offer?</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_4_answer_1">Yes</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_4_answer_2">No</string>

    <string name="john_scenario3_5"> You take a selfie, post it on social media, receive the discount and leave.</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_6"> Two weeks later . . .[TODO picture selfie on billboard in random country]</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_7"> Well actually I don’t have enough money left to buy something without discount. Lets head back home I have got to cook something for myself now.</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_8"> So lets see what do I have here, meat, rice, paprika. . . argh too many choices. Wait wait lets try this website I’ve recently heard about . . . Supercook.com yeah lets just add my groceries and see what I can cook with it.</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_9"> Ah a pop-up from supercook.com</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_10"> Choose which ingredient you want to use </string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_11"> Okay lets see I’d like something with this, okay supercook show me what you got.</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_12">The next morning..</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_13"> WHAT!? Wow I got 12 new mails!?[picture screen with spam mails]</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_14">But…how? How do they kn..wh..what was in that terms and condition from supercook?[picture terms and condition]</string>
    <string name="john_scenario3_15">Busted!</string>
</resources>
