<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GitLegit</string>

    <string name="john_introduction_info_1">Once upon a time…. John Doe was sick of all the gambling,
        sleeping day’s and walking nights in Last Vegas. </string>
    <string name="john_introduction_info_2">Tired of everything… he just wants to be like everyone else.
        A good job, full LinkedIn Profile, Very Active on Facebook. But the most important thing is finding a job!</string>
    <string name="john_introduction_1">Hello, my name is John I’m 32 years old.
        I’m at this point.Looking for a job. My Friends told me that getLinked is a good way to start searching for work.</string>
    <string name="john_introduction_2">Unfortunately, I don’t have any personal computer.
        Let’s go to the Internet Cafe. I need to go to the Internet Café in the neighborhood.</string>
    <string name="cleaner_job_title">looking for a cleaner</string>
    <string name="cleaner_job_description">Info: \n\'Optional Clean\' is an established cleaning company,
        looking for new employees to help out!\n\nWage:2300</string>
    <string name="volunteer_job_title">Looking for volunteers, (Minimum wage)</string>
    <string name="volunteer_job_description">We are a small non-profit organization and we are looking for volunteerd
    to help us build several houses for the poor. We are in desperate need of help so you will be receiving minimum wage pay
    If you are interested, please apply below!</string>
    <string name="fill_form_text_1">Alright, time to fill in my information! I have my ID card right here,
        I just need to enter it just as it is on my ID</string>
    <string name="search_engine_text1">Alright, let\'s search for the term: \'apply for job\'</string>
    <string name="search_engine_wrong_text">That didn\'t seem to be the correct search term</string>
    <string name="search_engine_no_results">No results found for \'%1$s\'</string>
    <string name="lawyer_job_title">Lawyer intern wanted!</string>
    <string name="lawyer_job_description">Info: \n\'BetterCallSomeLawyers\' has been active in the political
        field for decades, will you join them?\n\nWage: 4500 monthly</string>
    <string name="legit_job_title">Looking For: Assistent</string>
    <string name="legit_job_description">Info: \n\'FreshUp\' is an up and coming real estate agency, looking for an assistent to help us out\n\nWage:1500</string>

    <string name="fake_job_1_title">Looking for a Junior ProjectManager</string>
    <string name="fake_job_1_description">Experience in managing, apply now and join \'ProjectOr\' \n Wage: 5600 monthly</string>
    <string name="fake_job_2_title">In need of a welder</string>
    <string name="fake_job_2_description">Looking for a welder (experience optional) great benefits, apply for a position!\nWage: 2200 monthly</string>
    <string name="fake_job_3_title">Hiring HR interns</string>
    <string name="fake_job_3_description">Looking for students with an HR education, minimum of 6 months internships \n Wage: 1000 monthly</string>
    <string name="fake_job_4_title">Mechanic wanted</string>
    <string name="fake_job_4_description">Vehicle customization garage: \'FauxOriginal\', searching for new mechanic \n Wage: 3200 monthly</string>

</resources>
